[
    {
        "id":1,
        "question":"Enumeration is a",
        "options":["List of operations","List of String","Set of numbers","Set of legal value"],
        "correctoptions":"Set of legal value"
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question":"When static binding occurs?",
        "options":["compile time","load time","run time","none of"],
        "correctoptions":"compile time"
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question":"Which of the following is faster StringBuffer or StringBuilderStringBuilder",
        "options":["StringBuilder","StringBuffer","Both of the"],
        "correctoptions":"StringBuilder"
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question":"What is the defalut value of long variable",
        "options":["0","0.0","0L","nont defined"],
        "correctoptions":"0L"
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question":"What keyword is used to declare a variable that does not change its value?",
        "options":["final","static","const","var"],
        "correctoptions":"final"
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question":"What is the result of the expression:5+3*2?",
        "options":["10","11","13","26"],
        "correctoptions":"11"
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question":"What does JVM stand for?",
        "options":["Java Virtual Machine","Java Visual Model","Java Variable Manager"],
        "correctoptions":"Java Virtual Machine"
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question":"Which of these allows compiletime polymorphism?",
        "options":["Method overloading","Method overridding","Both"],
        "correctoptions":"Method overloading"
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question":"Which class is used to create a sever socket?",
        "options":["socket","ServerSocket","NetSocket","HostSocket"],
        "correctoptions":"ServerSocket"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question":"Which of the following is not a terminal operation in the stream APi?",
        "options":["foreach","map","reduce","collect"],
        "correctoptions":"map"
    }
]